backlinkbuilders.com 2010-06-07

# Privacy : Backlink Builders

## [Privacy](http://www.backlinkbuilders.com/privacy "Internet Marketing Blog on Privacy")

Posted by Backlink Builders

I respect your privacy and I am committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at my site http://www.backlinkbuilders.com. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers, I use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track userâ€™s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**E-mail Subscription**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to my posts via e-mail (powered by Feedburner), I ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for my usersâ€™ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the userâ€™s computer tied to information about the user. My site use cookies for tracking visitorsâ€™ activity. Some of my business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, I have no access to or control over these cookies, once I have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browserâ€™s settings section.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. I encourage my users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**  
I use outside ad companies to display ads on my site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and I do not have access to these information. I work with the ad companies: Google Adsense and many more. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding my privacy policy, please contact me by filling up the [contact form](http://www.backlinkbuilders.com/contact).
